(Raj:)-No.
-Star Wars?
(Raj:)No.
Um, Stan Lee. Oh, he was in those goofy
kung fu movies you love so much?
(Leonard:)That's Bruce Lee.
(Sheldon:)Oh.
(Penny:)So is this Bruce Lee's
nerdy brother, Stan?
(Howard:)Sheldon, why do you have all these
unopened paychecks in your desk?
(Sheldon:)Because most of the things I'm planning
to buy haven't been invented yet.
(Howard:)There must be thousands
of dollars here.
(Howard:)-Why don't you put it in the bank?
-I don't trust banks.
(Sheldon:)I believe that when the robots rise up,
ATMs will lead the charge.
(Howard:)You've also got something
from the Pasadena Municipal Court.
(Sheldon:)Undoubtedly yet another snide response
to my repeated letters...
(Sheldon:)...complaining that the flags in front of
the courthouse are in the wrong order.
(Sheldon:)It's supposed to be federal, state,
and then city of Pasadena.
(Penny:)I'm sorry, you sent more than one letter
about that?